whocalledme.com 2014-07-03

# Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors to whocalledme.com is important to us.

At whocalledme.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit whocalledme.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

#### What information do we collect?

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:  
(a) information about your visits to and use of this website;  
(b) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us and/or subscribing to our website services and/or email notifications; 

#### Using your personal data

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may use your personal information to:  
(a) improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;  
(b) to contact you about features and updates about whocalledme.com exclusively. 

#### Log files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

#### Cookies and web beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on whocalledme.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

#### DoubleClick DART cookies

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on whocalledme.com.  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to whocalledme.com and other sites on the Internet.   
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL -   
<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .......   
Google Adsense 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on whocalledme.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

whocalledme.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. whocalledme.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

#### Third party websites

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### Your consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

#### Changes to our privacy policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
